<module>
	<rawname>findmefollow</rawname>
	<name>Follow Me</name>
	<version>2.4.9</version>
	<changelog>
		*2.2.9* never allow extension to include itself as nnn# and create infinite loop
		*2.2.8* introduction of ringallv2 strategy that eliminates the double ring of the primary ext, REQUIRE CORE r3406
		*2.2.7* Changed to not set alertinfo value if already set from before hitting followme
		*2.2.6* Added BLKVM DB tree to fix inability to transfer a received call to another user, and make NODEST stuff work overall
		*2.4.5* Modified NODEST stuff to improve some cases where it was still failing, and improve '#' transfer scenarios
		*2.4.4* Add NODEST so that destination (often vm) is not taken if called from queue or ringgroup
		*2.4.3* Sanity check for prefing that if not set or there, it won't ring the extension forever (should not happen)
		*2.4.2* Modified flyover help - since moh works with confirmation now
		*2.4.1* Added sound files for default confirmation messages
		2.4: First release for FreePBX 2.2 - Fixed compatibility issue with new UI
		2.3.1: removed checkastman
		2.3: First release for 2.2, fixed minor display issues
		2.2.5: fixed so extension number is put into empty lists
		2.2.4: moved require_once() in functions.php, was breaking other stuff
		2.2.3: full path in require_once to keep retrieve_conf from dieing
		2.2.2: bug fix = should be ==
		2.2.1: Use astdb for some settings
		2.2.0: Add Pre-Ring
		2.1.5: Fix bug #1142
		2.1.4: Code cleanup
	</changelog>
	<type>setup</type>
	<category>Inbound Call Control</category>
	<description>
		Much like a ring group, but works on individual extensions. When someone calls the extension, it can be setup to ring for a number of seconds before trying to ring other extensions and/or external numbers, or to ring all at once, or in other various 'hunt' configurations. Most commonly used to ring someone's cell phone if they don't answer their extension.
	</description>
	<menuitems>
		<findmefollow>Follow Me</findmefollow>
	</menuitems>
	<location>release/2.3/findmefollow-2.4.8.tgz</location>
	<info>http://aussievoip.com.au/wiki/freePBX-FollowMe</info>
	<md5sum>a4f809f3907a72f4b88f6ba007c513c0</md5sum>
</module>
